[{"answer": "And the NRA fires back at President Obama on guns.", "docId": "130123pmt", "aSentId": 7, "question": "What difference at this point does it make?", "qSentId": 6}, {"answer": "What I thought is still so many questions that went unanswered and frankly some unsatisfactory answers.", "docId": "130123pmt", "aSentId": 43, "question": "What was your verdict?", "qSentId": 42}, {"answer": "Piers, first of all, that's not what I'm saying.", "docId": "130123pmt", "aSentId": 70, "question": "Well, where do we go with this?", "qSentId": 69}, {"answer": "I fully agree that the whole goal of this is to make sure we get to the bottom of it so that it doesn't happen again and also so that we make sure -- I mean, one of the things, of course, we learned as well is we had someone in custody in Tunisia, that person has been released and we want to hold those accountable for -- who committed these horrible murders on our people.", "docId": "130123pmt", "aSentId": 91, "question": "And I'm sure you would agree with that, right?", "qSentId": 90}, {"answer": "Well, I think there are legitimate questions that still need to be answered.", "docId": "130123pmt", "aSentId": 100, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 99}, {"answer": "I do agree with that.", "docId": "130123pmt", "aSentId": 111, "question": "Do you agree with that?", "qSentId": 110}, {"answer": "So we're going -- I don't think it's quite analogous to compare what happened during the Bush administration with what's happening right now.", "docId": "130123pmt", "aSentId": 128, "question": "When you take that line of political argument, should everybody just be fired every time any intelligence turns out to be not quite right?", "qSentId": 127}, {"answer": "-- a blanket standard of measures.", "docId": "130123pmt", "aSentId": 131, "question": "Well, why not?", "qSentId": 130}, {"answer": "Because this is the Dick -- Dick Durbin argument from earlier today, this is what we heard from Dick Durbin earlier when he was questioning Secretary of State Clinton.", "docId": "130123pmt", "aSentId": 134, "question": "Why not?", "qSentId": 133}, {"answer": "But the bottom line is --", "docId": "130123pmt", "aSentId": 139, "question": "What's the difference?", "qSentId": 138}, {"answer": "Dana.", "docId": "130123pmt", "aSentId": 143, "question": "-- where are the mistakes made?", "qSentId": 142}, {"answer": "I'm talking about what I --", "docId": "130123pmt", "aSentId": 169, "question": "Are we going to talk about the Bush years or are we going to talk about what happened in Benghazi?", "qSentId": 168}, {"answer": "Yes, I do.", "docId": "130123pmt", "aSentId": 171, "question": "Do you not think, Piers -- do you not think that it's legitimate to ask who manipulated these talking points?", "qSentId": 170}, {"answer": "There are many legitimate questions.", "docId": "130123pmt", "aSentId": 176, "question": "Then why aren't we talking about that?", "qSentId": 175}, {"answer": "I think it's a serious charge and I think it's a false charge.", "docId": "130123pmt", "aSentId": 190, "question": "Do you believe that at any stage either Susan Rice or Hillary Clinton has deliberately lied or deliberately misled the American people?", "qSentId": 189}, {"answer": "Well, one of the interesting things about this, Piers, is that you asked me if I liked any of these.", "docId": "130123pmt", "aSentId": 221, "question": "And now you have time to think about that, was there nothing that the president came out with in any of the 23 executive orders or any of the other proposals that you could at least consider?", "qSentId": 220}, {"answer": "Including the NRA as well.", "docId": "130123pmt", "aSentId": 225, "question": "Why would you -- why would you not like background checks?", "qSentId": 224}, {"answer": "Wait a minute.", "docId": "130123pmt", "aSentId": 243, "question": "So did you mislead me last time?", "qSentId": 242}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "130123pmt", "aSentId": 269, "question": "What good are laws if people don't follow them?", "qSentId": 268}, {"answer": "I don't maintain anything.", "docId": "130123pmt", "aSentId": 271, "question": "So you still maintain that we just have to put more and more guns out there and America will be safer?", "qSentId": 270}, {"answer": "And Piers, let me tell you something.", "docId": "130123pmt", "aSentId": 276, "question": "Do you believe that?", "qSentId": 275}, {"answer": "Let me -- let me answer you.", "docId": "130123pmt", "aSentId": 281, "question": "-- would lead to less gun crime?", "qSentId": 280}, {"answer": "Well, I mean, no.", "docId": "130123pmt", "aSentId": 313, "question": "Now, PJ, have you heard any convincing argument as to why that kind of weapon should remain in civilian hands?", "qSentId": 312}, {"answer": "Well, I mean, as you look at war, you know, there's no difference anymore in the current way that wars are fought between the front lines and the rear guard.", "docId": "130123pmt", "aSentId": 323, "question": "What did you make of that, PJ?", "qSentId": 322}, {"answer": "Well, I would say the contradiction also exists with you, though.", "docId": "130123pmt", "aSentId": 341, "question": "Why would they not be able to be as effective as many men in combat?", "qSentId": 340}, {"answer": "Well, you can't attribute one particular event like this to climate change.", "docId": "130123pmt", "aSentId": 418, "question": "In all your time as a meteorologist, have you a sense now that we are going through a genuine climatic change in the weather?", "qSentId": 417}, {"answer": "I don't think there's any -- I think you're better off --", "docId": "130123pmt", "aSentId": 430, "question": "What do you say to that?", "qSentId": 429}, {"answer": "I say you look at the peer reviewed literature.", "docId": "130123pmt", "aSentId": 465, "question": "What do you say to that?", "qSentId": 464}, {"answer": "No, CO2 is rising.", "docId": "130123pmt", "aSentId": 475, "question": "You wouldn't dispute there's been increased acceleration in CO2, right?", "qSentId": 474}, {"answer": "Yes, Piers, I haven't met Mark.", "docId": "130123pmt", "aSentId": 487, "question": "Michael, over to you?", "qSentId": 486}, {"answer": "Just like I just thawed out, so will the Midwest and the northeast.", "docId": "130123pmt", "aSentId": 516, "question": "Lee, what's the forecast for the next few days?", "qSentId": 515}, {"answer": "I got two battery packs in here.", "docId": "130123pmt", "aSentId": 524, "question": "ORGAN: I hear you are wearing a battery packed heated jacket?", "qSentId": 523}, {"answer": "I knitted them myself while we were away.", "docId": "130123pmt", "aSentId": 530, "question": "Did ABC find a few more dollars to finish off the gloves?", "qSentId": 529}, {"answer": "Guns are very serious instruments of survival and defense.", "docId": "130123pmt", "aSentId": 573, "question": "What's your view about the debate?", "qSentId": 572}, {"answer": "I don't know if I'll give you an answer that will satisfy your sense of -- you know, sane logic.", "docId": "130123pmt", "aSentId": 601, "question": "Can you give me an answer?", "qSentId": 600}, {"answer": "Well, you know, yes.", "docId": "130123pmt", "aSentId": 616, "question": "How do you possibly defend yourselves?", "qSentId": 615}, {"answer": "OAKAM: In case of point of (inaudible), that literally an extension of the tradition of -- there was an old blue grass song called \"Knoxville Girl,\" where for no reason -- it actually goes back to Irish guys who wrote folk songs.", "docId": "130123pmt", "aSentId": 641, "question": "But do you believe that any musician or movie star or movie maker or music producer, do they have any responsibility in terms of rhetoric about guns or the portrayal of them in movies?", "qSentId": 640}, {"answer": "No, they're not.", "docId": "130123pmt", "aSentId": 653, "question": "These aren't unexploded grenades, right?", "qSentId": 652}, {"answer": "I felt getting that footage was very revealing.", "docId": "130123pmt", "aSentId": 702, "question": "Eddie, when you got that footage, what did you feel about it?", "qSentId": 701}, {"answer": "Well, I mean, clearly, I was incredibly shocked and saddened.", "docId": "130123pmt", "aSentId": 715, "question": "What were your emotions then?", "qSentId": 714}, {"answer": "Well, I have to say, first off, that I'm a filmmaker.", "docId": "130123pmt", "aSentId": 726, "question": "More guns would lead to more safety at schools?", "qSentId": 725}]